Encore Encore
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu she.
The upper right corner is the internal organs.
Nice collection!
yarusake
Good morning!
Soon...
I'm going to be in Nass Highland Park for a public recording of Gargartuuk.
We have already finished rehearsal.
We're putting on our makeup, but everyone has their own style.
Kira is doing her makeup.
She's always here.
It's the last time.
And it's always the same backstage.
Backstage.
What?
What's over there?
Yeah.
There's one place that's a little...
It's a little smaller than the one we're in right now.
It's a little smaller.
You sit in the same place every time.
Misaki's always a little...
That's it.
Misaki sits there or there...
She's in the simple seat.
That's right.
It's not the same color here.
There are still seats here.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, there are.
Oh, my God, what am I going to do?
So...
I'm going to do Yoko's makeup.
What shall we do today?
Let's talk about it.Let's talk.
This is gonna put us on fast forward.
You don't want to do it? No, I don't.
But I'd love to film you at dinner.
It's delicious.
Yeah, we all love it.
I've got a little bit of a bear problem.
A bear!
Yuka-chan's called a bear.
It's a bear.
Yuka, you're fine either way.
It's a bear!
Bridges, bridges, bridges...
And rain and rain.
Rain and rain.
Rain is different
And rain... You don't get it, do you?
You don't get it, do you?
Let's read it in literature.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's someone waiting for you near the bed.
That's...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't have time.
There's no time.
Who's on the phone?
Me and Misaki.
We're going on a trip to America.
What? You don't have any money.
Wait, which way are you talking about?
This way, right?
Misaki said she doesn't have any money.
Talk about lack of money.
It's too graphic.It's too graphic.
What do you think? Killer.
What do you think?
What do you really think?
I want to talk to you about money.
I'm scared to death.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I love you guys. I don't have any money.
I don't have money. I don't have money.
You said it yourself.
Killer.
Oh, I'm telling you.
No money.
We were just talking about going.
Don't get me wrong, guys.
Don't get me wrong.
It's okay.
Yes, the first part is over.
The weather was great.
It was hot, wasn't it?
It was always raining.
It sure was.
It's been a while since we've had sunshine.
How was it? Did you have fun?
It was fun.
In the first part, during the countdown, encore, and choo-choo, I heard a "fur" sound.
From the fans?
Yes, I'm sure.
It sounded like a summery song.
What will the second part be about?
Yes, I'm going to eat lunch.
I'm going to have lunch.
Your cheeks are so red.
It's not good.It's hot.
It's hot.
35 degrees.
37?
It's worse for hot people.
That's for sure.
We shouldn't be talking about how hot it is.
That's right.
Please put on a hat.
I'll do my best.
Seriously, this angle is not good.
Lean left and walk.
Put your lower leg down.
Okay, I'm going to have lunch now.
Yes!
Udon noodles!
Udon noodles today.
Your cheeks are still red.
Watching over them
Sweetie!
Yes, sir!
Let's eat!
Yes, ma'am!
Bon appétit.
It's okay, I want to watch over them.
No, thank you.
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
It's lunchtime, guys.
Oh, man.
Thank you so much.
I was filming.
Let's all eat together.
Let's join hands.
Bon appétit!
Wow!Oh, my God!
Shut up.
Shut up!
You're too scary!
What's with that reaction?
That's what I don't like.
You don't like that look.
Shut up.
It's a little bit fake.
It's like, "Lip mash" or something.
What's the matter with you?
I told you, he's the one.
As I said, he's the one.
He's the one.
It's the person himself
Himself
The person himself/herself
Wow, that's not in the video.
I'm not gonna hit you like that.
Shut up, he's eating.
He's eating it!
I'm not eating it.
You're eating it.
I can't eat it.
Yes, you can.
I can eat it if I want to.
If I don't like it...
I won't eat it by myself.
Let's go eat this tomato.
No, but...
I don't want to.but (I don't care)
I don't think that's such a good idea.
You're the wrong person to ask.
Don't worry.
I'll do Minami.
Let's go to Tomatogari.
If Ichigo's there, I'll go.
But...
I'm not good with red.
Oh!
One time, Kaja.
hey
Please use it
Oh no.
just now.
signboard
It's full of...
I'm so happy
I'm so excited
around here
Good genre
Wait, who do you want to go to the concert? If we're all going...
Let's go to Creepy Nuts!
Chenille.
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Allergy Award
Do you wish you could have been
Or to watch
How to make excuses
I'm finally learning
I'm getting it.
A soft head.
Not fine.
I don't need a soft head
Headhead
head
Like Mr. Ado.
I know.
I want to go to Ado so bad.
Really?
Can I ask you something?
It's so funny.
Next time you're home.
I have something I want to do.
A full day of streaming.
It's gonna be tight.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Eat your breakfast.
Vlog delivery
Naomi Watanabe's delivery
I haven't decided yet.
Bath-like
Home time delivery
If you do it for a day
you'll start to look like you're taking a bath even if you don't think about it.
That's for sure.
That's what we're all doing.
Stay somewhere else.
We'll stay at home for the whole day.
All of us.
We did over 24 hours of streaming.
Eight of us.
On the move.
You know, there are people who do this a lot.
You know what I mean.
24 hours?
How about going to bed?
In the morning or straight to sleep.
Shin-chan.
Have you ever seen a 24-hour cellbi?Have you ever seen a 24-hour serbi or something like that?
Oh, selvie.
I understand.
I'm going to sleep for a bit.
If I fall asleep, I'll be punished.
If I fall asleep, I'm going home.
And I'm going on a mission.
I'd like to do it together... with everyone.
I think we all could use a little sleep.
We'll take turns.
Four seconds, maybe.
Give me a hand, give me a hand.
That's what I'm talking about.
Maybe I should splash some water on him.
I don't want to drown.
But I want to stay the night.
You know, that time...
I was in bondage
I had a job to do.
I was on a mission.
If it's a Corona, we'll wear masks.
I'd wear a mask.
It's so much freer now.
Like when we ate dinner.
I'm doing this to Shi-chan.
Girls Revolution 2.
Where do you want to go?
Miyako Island.
I've always wanted to go there.
Okinawa or Miyako Island
Where is Miyako Island?
Okinawa
There's no room in Okinawa.
Somewhere like that
Izu?
Atami areaAtami area
What can water do
There is an ocean
With everyone
Sexy beach
If you want a sexy beach, Miyakojima is fine.
Night view video
I mean...
A lot of self-research
But...
I'm going to get so mad.
I was going to be so pissed
I'm gonna be so pissed.
She's opening the nest right up.
Mother
A view of the girls
She's gonna be pissed.
I'm just being honest.
Even if you're not working...
I don't want to stay here.
I want to stay at the Fish House.
All of us.
With a bath in the room?
With an open-air bath.
How about that?
Let's go, guys!
Kumamoto is a nice place, isn't it?
And a ryokan.
One person is gone.
One of them fell asleep.
And a baby.
A big baby.
He's sleeping.
Thank you for dinner.
Can I show it to you?
That, too.That, too.
That's not what it means.
Give me your change, please.
I know.
I want to challenge myself.
Music
music
Smile More Toward Me
I need you baby